http://www.yogaheart.com/privacy-policy/

Gentle Yoga, Chair Yoga and MP3 Yoga
for Boomers, Seniors and Beginners of All AgesJust another WordPress site
Privacy Policy
By accessing this site, you indicate your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
Use of Collected Information
We do not sell or distribute our private mailing list to any other parties. However, we may contact you from time to time on behalf of our partners in order to let you know about related, pertinent information and special offers that we truly feel will be of added value to you on your path. If you would like to opt out of future promotional materials from us, you may indicate this preference by following the unsubscribe instructions at the end of such email communications.
We may disclose information about our users, including personally identifiable information, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Web site and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Web site. We also may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of our users. We may sell, transfer, or otherwise disclose user information, including personally identifiable information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of substantially all assets, or other corporate change respecting the Web site.
Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors
Some of our Web pages may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors and Customers should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
We may sometimes offer content that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties.  By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity.  We have no control over these third parties’ use of this information. We will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.
Reviewing and Correcting Your Information:
To access the personally identifiable information that this site has collected about you online, or to correct factual errors in such information, please contact us via our contact page.
Changes to Privacy Policy
We may, from time to time, update this privacy notice. We will post material changes at our website, so we encourage you to check back periodically.
Questions/Concerns?
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via our contact page.
Effective Date: This notice was created on October 1, 2015.
Recent Blogs
Do Your Knees Bend…Backward?
Yoga is Like Sex!
Welcome to the World of Yoga
Yoga: Adding Balance to Your Life
Sign up for free sample video
© 2015  Susan Winter Ward and Yoga for the Young at Heart, LLC
